brandreward.com 2018-12-13

# Privacy Policy

## Brandreward Privacy Policy

### General Information

Privacy is important at Brandreward (the “Company”, “our” or “we”). We fully understand that as a Publisher, Advertiser or End User; there is a need to know how your personal information about your website and/or browsing behavior is being collected, how it is used and how it is shared; when you visit the Brandreward website (the “Website”), engage in Brandreward services (the “Services”) or use the Brandreward technology (the “Software”).

The following contents of our Privacy Policy explains how information collected by Brand Reward (Hong Kong) Limited is used and shared.

Last updated: November 22nd 2016

### Sections

#### I. Terminology

  * Advertisers:

All persons or entities providing goods and/or services to End Users and entitled to access and use our Service or Software.

  * Brandreward Manual Links:

Tracking links that allow the Brandreward Software to match data from Advertisers, End Users and Publishers.

  * End Users:

All persons or entities that visit or interact with Publishers using Brandreward Services or Software.

  * Identifiable Personal Information (“IPI”):

Information such as full name, home address, telephone number, social media account or email address that is uniquely identifiable and linked to an individual person.

  * Non-Identifiable Personal Information (“NPI”): 

Information such as IP address, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access dates and times, referring website addresses, online transactions and browsing and search activity that cannot be uniquely linked to an individual person.

  * Publishers:

All persons or entities registered and entitled to access and use our Service or Software.

  * Website Visitors:

All online visitors or entities that engage and/or interact with our Website.

#### II. General statement of use

Visitors to our Website may have access to public information, but only persons or entities that are successfully registered will have full access to Brandreward Service and Software. Brandreward Service and Software is available for use only by persons or entities that are registered as a Publisher. We provide basic Service and Software to certain Advertisers that require assistance.

#### III. How to contact us

If you are a Website Visitor, Advertiser, Publisher or End User and have an urgent issue or question then please email us at support [at] brandreward [dot] com. For questions that have not been fully addressed or additional feedback regarding the Brandreward Privacy Policy, feel free to send us feedback through our [Contact Form](mailto:support@brandreward.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Feedback).

#### IV. Information collection and use

##### A. How is data collected?

##### 1\. Tracking Technology

###### a. Cookies Technology

We use a technology called “cookies” when any visitor interacts with our Website. These invisible cookies are left on a visitor’s computer and helps the Brandreward Website identify a returning visitor on our Website. This technology also allows our system to collect basic information that helps our team to offer better Services and our Website to provide each unique visitor with a more customized user experience.

More information regarding “cookies” can be found through the following articles:

  * • www.iab-performance-marketing-explained.net
  * • http://www.allaboutcookies.org
  * • For Microsoft Internet Explorer: http://www.microsoft.com/infor/cookies.htm
  * • For Mozilla Firefox: http://support.mozilla.com/en-USkb/Options+window+-
  * • Google Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647&p=cpn_cookies

###### b. JavaScript Technology

In some instances, Brandreward applies a technology called “JavaScript” which allows for our Website and Software to record data and interact with a Web User, Publisher, Advertiser or End User. This technology allows for the Brandreward Website and Software to offer an optimized and personalized experience for each type of user. Sites that are Brandreward enabled with JavaScript means that a Brandreward snippet of code is added to a Publisher’s site and will provide feedback to the Brandreward Software for purposes of matching data to each unique publisher.

##### 2\. Website Visitors

Data is collected when a website visitor is directed to our Website and starts to interact with our Website, such as opening different pages of the Website, account creation, filling out contact forms or opening another website referred by the content on our Website. We use cookies and JavaScript technologies to collect NPI and IPI data.

If you would like to be removed from data collection, please contact us through this [Contact Form](mailto:support@brandreward.com?subject=Removal%20from%20Data%20Collection).

##### 3\. Advertisers

NPI Data is collected when Publisher or End Users that originated from our Website reaches an Advertiser’s website.

##### 4\. Publishers

There are several ways that data is collected from publishers; including when publishers visit our Website (NPI), input information during signup (IPI), use our Software (NPI and IPI), when End Users interact with a Brandreward Software enabled Publisher site (NPI and IPI) and when publishers communicate with our team members when using our Services (NPI and IPI). Cookies technology and JavaScript technology are used to collect such data.

##### 5\. End Users

NPI data is collected from End Users when they click on a Publisher’s site content that has been enabled using Brandreward Software.

##### B. USE OF COLLECTED DATA

##### 1\. Identifiable Personal Information (IPI) Data

IPI Data is encrypted with our internal security measures and used for internal purposes. There will be no instance in which the data will be used outside of the original purpose and intent of when the website visitor was asked to release such IPI information. The data will be used to improve the Website’s usability and user experience for each unique visitor.

In the rare case that there are updates to our Privacy Policy regarding use of IPI Data, we will communicate all related modifications through email and visible on the Publisher Dashboard.

##### 2\. Non-Identifiable Personal Information (NPI) Data

NPI data is collected while a website visitor is interacting with our Website. This data is encrypted with our internal security measures and only used internally to help access the demographics of our Website. The data is used to improve the Website’s usability and user experience.

In the rare case that there are updates to our Privacy Policy regarding use of NPI Data, we will communicate all related modifications through email and visible on the Publisher Dashboard.

##### 3\. Do Not Track Option

We respect your right to privacy and also offer the Do Not Track Option, please let us know through this [Contact Form](mailto:support@brandreward.com?subject=Do%20Not%20Track%20Option). However, please note that in order to use the Brandreward Software or Services, some IPI and NPI Data must be enabled and allowed for Advertisers, Publishers or End Users.

##### 4\. Children & Data

Brandreward takes the protection of children online as a very serious matter. If a child under the age of 13 happens to interact with the Brandreward Website, Service or Software, IPI or NPI data might unintentionally be collected. If this occurs, it is highly recommended that the parent or guardian please contact us here, so we can find and remove this information from our records.

##### C. Data modification & security

##### 1\. Modifying Data

Data is rarely modified unless requested by the Website Visitor, Advertiser, Publisher or End User. In the case that we require modification, we will first request and confirm approval from the relevant party prior to taking any actions related to data modification. A Publisher has the ability to modify their individual information upon login but must communicate through the Services Team to modify thereafter.

##### 2\. Data Disclosure

###### a. IPI Data

Data privacy is very important at Brandreward. We do not disclose any detailed or specific IPI Data with any third parties and have strict internal disclosure policies in place. For the purpose of lead generation, we will occasionally provide aggregated overall IPI Data for geographical regions and overall revenue information. There may be instances in which we are required or compelled under applicable law or regulations or due to legal process to disclose information to government agencies or officials.

###### b. NPI Data

Aggregated basic NPI Data is shared with third parties, consisting of partnership agencies, technology and services. This NPI Data is in the form of graphical charts and system performance. Some basic aggregated NPI data can also be included for lead generation efforts, including aggregated generic traffic. There may be instances in which we are required or compelled under applicable law or regulations or due to legal process to disclose information to government agencies or officials.

###### c. Retention

IPI and NPI Data are retained for an indefinite amount of time unless formally requested by an individual website visitor, advertiser, publisher or end user to be deleted from our internal records. Please note IPI Data is retained in our records, even if a publisher does not engage the use of the Brandreward Software or Services but has provided IPI Data during account creation or any other steps that require IPI Data.

#### V. Security

Data privacy is very important at Brandreward. There are strict technological and physical company protocols to ensure data is kept internal and for the sole purposes as discussed in our Privacy Policy. IPI Data is especially important and sharing is restricted and requires full-consent from the individual publisher, advertiser, end user or website visitor. Please note that there may be instances of hardware or software failure and other uncontrollable factors that may still present a risk for Brandreward to compromise NPI and IPI Data security. Use of the Brandreward Software or Services means acknowledgement of this risk. If you believe that NPI or IPI Data has been shared without consent, please contact us here.

#### VI. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Brandreward retains the right to modify or replace terms within this Privacy Policy at any time or on an ad hoc basis. Indication of any such modifications or replacements within this Privacy Policy will be through email communication and through the Publisher Dashboard.
